Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Affiliated bodies correspondence and reports, 1907-1952; Series 2; 47 microfilm reels
  - Joint Council correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2
    Joint councils were organized to coordinate the activities of local unions within a specific geographic area, usually a single city and its environs, though sometimes an entire state. The functions of the councils have narrowed somewhat over the years as trade divisions and conferences have assumed more and more responsibilities in the fields of organizing and negotiation of contracts. They serve as an arbiter in disputes of member locals. The correspondence deals with such subjects as affiliations of new locals and suspension of others, problems with local officers, political action, jurisdictional disputes, bargaining problems, difficulties with central labor bodies, and requests for statistical information. Each council is represented by only a small amount of material, most of which dates in the 1940's.
    Arranged numerically by joint council number and chronological thereunder.
    - Joint Council #7, San Francisco, California, 1908, 1912-1915, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 12)
    - Joint Council #9, North and South Carolina, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 12a)
    - Joint Council #10, Boston, Massachusetts, 1908, 1913-1914, 1942-; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 13)
    - Joint Council #11, Lake County, Indiana, 1941-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 14)
    - Joint Council #13, St. Louis, Missouri, 1912-1915, 1942-; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 15)
    - Joint Council #15, Albany, New York, 1914; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 16)
    - Joint Council #16, New York, New York, 1907, 1912-1915; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 17)
    - Joint Council #17, Rochester, New York, 1938-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 18)
    - Joint Council #18, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1913-1915, 1921-1915; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 19)
    - Joint Council #19, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 20)
    - Joint Council #20, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 21)
    - Joint Council #23, Butte, Montana, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 22)
    - Joint Council #25, Chicago, Illinois, 1907-1908, 1912-; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 23)
    - Joint Council #26 Cincinnati, Ohio, 1914-1915; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 24)
    - Joint Council #26 Cincinnati, Ohio, 1946-1948; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 56, Segment 25)
    - Joint Council #26 Cincinnati, Ohio, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 1)
    - Joint Council #28, Seattle, Washington, 1914, 1935- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 2)
    - Joint Council #30, Columbus, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 3)
    - Joint Council #31, West Frankfort, Illinois, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 4)
    - Joint Council #32, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 5)
    - Joint Council #32, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 6)
    - Joint Council #34, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 7)
    - Joint Council #34, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 8)
    - Joint Council #36, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 9)
    - Joint Council #37, Portland, Oregon, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 10)
    - Joint Council #38, Sacramento, California, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 11)
    - Joint Council #39, Belleville, Illinois, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 12)
    - Joint Council #40, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 13)
    - Joint Council #40, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1946-1948 /; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 14)
    - Joint Council #40, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1949-1952 undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 15)
    - Joint Council #41, Cleveland, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 16)
    - Joint Council #42, Los Angeles, California, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 57, Segment 17)
    - Joint Council #43, Detroit, Michigan, 1912, 1941- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 1)
    - Joint Council #44, Toledo, Ohio, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 2)
    - Joint Council #45, Des Moines, Iowa, 1942, 1946- • 1950; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 3)
    - Joint Council #46, Buffalo, New York, 1907-1908, 1942-; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 4)
    - Joint Council #47, Akron, Ohio, 1941-1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 5)
    - Joint Council #48, Duluth and Superior, Minnesota, 1941-1952 1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 6)
    - Joint Council #49, Canton, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 7)
    - Joint Council #50, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 8)
    - Joint Council #52, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1941-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 9)
    - Joint Council #53, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1913-1914» 1941-; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 10)
    - Joint Council #54, Denver, Colorado, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 11)
    - Joint Council #55, Washington, D. C., 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 12)
    - Joint Council #56, Kansas City, Missouri, 1908, 1942- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 13)
    - Joint Council #57, Clarksburg, West Virginia, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 14)
    - Joint Council #58, Houston, Texas, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 15)
    - Joint Council #59, LaSalle, Illinois, 1942-1945; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 16)
    - Joint Council #60, Appleton, Wisconsin, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 16)
    - Joint Council #61, Dayton, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 17)
    - Joint Council #62, Baltimore, Maryland, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 18)
    - Joint Council #63, Wausau, Wisconsin, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 19)
    - Joint Council #64, New Haven, Connecticut, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 20)
    - Joint Council #65, Peoria, Illinois, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 21)
    - Joint Council #66, Springfield, Illinois, 1941-1948; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 22)
    - Joint Council #67, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 23)
    - Joint Council #68, Atlanta, Georgia, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 24)
    - Joint Council #69, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1915, 1941-1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 25)
    - Joint Council #69, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 26)
    - Joint Council #70, Syracuse, New York, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 27)
    - Joint Council #71, Phoenix, Arizona, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 28)
    - Joint Council #72, Albany, New York, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 29)
    - Joint Council #73, Essex County, New Jersey, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 30)
    - Joint Council #75, South Bend, Indiana, 1943-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 31)
    - Joint Council #76, Evansville, Indiana, 1943-1949; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 32)
    - Joint Council #78, St. Charles, Missouri, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 33)
    - Joint Council #79, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 34)
    - Joint Council #80, Dallas, Texas, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 35)
    - Joint Council #81, Omaha, Nebraska, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 36)
    - Joint Council #82, Fargo, North Dakota, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 58, Segment 37)
    - Joint Council #83, Richmond, Virginia, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 59, Segment 1)
    - Joint Council #84, Charleston, West Virginia, 1948-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 59, Segment 2)
    - Joint Council #85, Jacksonville, Florida, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 59, Segment 3)
    - Joint Council #86, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 59, Segment 4)
    - Joint Council #87, Tennessee and Paducah, Kentucky, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 59, Segment 5)
    - Joint Council #93, Louisiana, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Reel 59, Segment 6)
  - Area and state conferences correspondence and reports, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3
    These organizations were established along geographical lines for the purpose of conducting organizing and bargaining activities on a large scale. Four national area conferences exist: Central, Eastern, Southern and Western, of which the last three only are represented in the Papers. In addition, there are several smaller area and state conferences. The files contain correspondence, minutes, and reports concerned mainly with organizing, bargaining, strikes, jurisdictional conflicts with other unions, by-laws of the conferences, financial reports, and transcripts of hearings and decisions by government agencies. Individual filee are quite fragmentary; only for the Southern Conference of Teamsters is there any appreciable amount of material.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of conference and chronological thereunder.
    - All Conferences - Editors, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 7)
    - Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 8)
    - Illinois Teamsters Conference, 1946-1950; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 9)
    - Indiana Conference of Teamsters, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 10)
    - Iowa Conference of Teamsters, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 11)
    - Michigan Conference of Teamsters, 1943, 194 1-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 12)
    - Mid-Atlantic Conference of Teamsters, 1945-1947; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 13)
    - Mid-Eastern Conference, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 14)
    - Minnesota Conference of Teamsters, 1941-1942, 1946, 1948, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 15)
    - Missouri-Kansas Conference of Teamsters, 1947-1950; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 16)
    - New England Council of Teamsters, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 17)
    - New York State Teamsters Council, 1943-1946, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 18)
    - Ohio Conference of Teamsters, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 19)
    - Ohio Conference of Teamsters - Transcripts of Quarterly Meetings, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 20)
    - Piedmont Conference of Teamsters (North and South Carolina), 1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 21)
    - Southeastern Conference of Teamsters, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 22)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 23)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 24)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 59, Segment 25)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1947, January - September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 1)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1947 October - 1948 February; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 2)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1948, March - December; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 3)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 4)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 5)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1946, A-Z; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 6)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1947, A-Z (1st 3 quarters only); Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 7)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1947, A-Z (Oct.-Dec. only); Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 8)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 9)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 10)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 11)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 12)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Financial Statements, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 13)
    - Southern Conference of Teamsters - Strike, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 14)
    - Texas Conference of Teamsters, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 15)
    - Tri-States Drivers Council (Iowa, South Dakota, and Nebraska), 1943-1944, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 16)
    - Western Conference of Teamsters, 1944, 1946. -1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 17)
    - Wisconsin Conference of Teamsters, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Reel 60, Segment 18)
  - Trade Divisions correspondence, 1939-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4
    These are organizations of teamsters first established in the late 1930's on a state, regional, or national basis and along trade lines. Though some of these organizations are called "council" or "conference" rather than "trade division", they are all organized on the basis of a particular trade and thereby are differentiated from the area and state conferences. Trade divisions gradually took over much of the organizing and bargaining activity on a regional or national scale; these activities are the subject matter of the trade division files. The files include some correspondence but also considerable mimeographed and printed material such as reports, minutes of meetings, agreements, and contract summaries. The Central States Drivers Council file is quite extensive, but the majority of the trade divisions are thinly represented in the collection.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of trade and chronological thereunder.
    - All Trade Divisions, 1940, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 19)
    - Automotive: National Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Trades Division, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 20)
    - Automotive: Central States Petroleum and Automotive Conference, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 21)
    - Bakery: National Bakery Conference, 1944, 1948- 1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 22)
    - Cannery: General Agreements and Miscellaneous, 1940, 1945- 1946, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 23)
    - Cannery: National Cannery Conference, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 24)
    - Cannery: California State Council of Cannery Unions, 1943-1945; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 60, Segment 25)
    - Cannery: California State Council of Cannery Unions, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 1)
    - Cannery: California State Council of Cannery Unions, 1947-1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 2)
    - Cannery: Washington State Council of Cannery Unions, 1939; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 3)
    - Cannery: Western Council of Cannery and Food Process Workers, 1947, 1950, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 4)
    - Chauffeurs: National Trade Division of Chauffeurs and Taxicab Drivers, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 5)
    - City Cartage: Iowa and Nebraska Statewide Strike (arranged by Local number), 1949, Nov.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 6)
    - Commercial Drivers: Pennsylvania Commercial Drivers Conference, 1941-1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 7)
    - Construction: National Division of Building Materials and Construction Drivers, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 8)
    - Construction: New York State Construction and Supply Drivers Council, 1942-1944,1948-1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 9)
    - Dairy: International Conference of Dairy Employees and Mid States - East Coast Dairy Conference, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 10)
    - Dairy: Upper New York State Dairy Employees Council, 1947-1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 11)
    - Fruit: National Conference of Fresh Fruit, Vegetable and Produce Industry, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 12)
    - Fruit: Mid-West Area of Commission House Conference of Produce and Fresh Fruit, Vegetable and Frozen Food Industry, 1947-1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 13)
    - Government: Federal, State, Municipal and Public Service Employees National Division, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 14)
    - Over-the-Road: National Over-the-Road Conference, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 15)
    - Over-the-Road: National Over-the-Road Conference, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 16)
    - Over-the-Road: National Over-the-Road Conference, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 17)
    - Over-the-Road: Atlantic Sea Coast Organizing Committee, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 18)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1940-1941; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 19)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 61, Segment 20)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1943, Jan,-Aug.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 1)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1943, Sept.-Nov.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 2)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1943, Dec., undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 3)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1944, Jan.-July; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 4)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1944, Aug.-Dec.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 5)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1945, Jan.-June; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 6)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1945, July-Sept.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 7)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1945, Oct.-Dec.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 8)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1946, Jan.-June; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 9)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1946, July-Dec.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 10)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 11)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 12)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1949, Jan.-Oct.; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 62, Segment 13)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1949, Nov.-Dec.,undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 1)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 2)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 3)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Akron Owner Operators, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 4)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Mailing List of Ohio Trucking Companies, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 5)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Minutes of Meetings, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 6)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Strikes (arranged by Local number): Locals 1-199, 1949 November; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 7-35)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Strikes (arranged by Local number): Locals 200-399, 1949 November; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 36-59)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Strikes (arranged by Local number): Locals 400-599, 1949 November; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 60-89)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Strikes (arranged by Local number): Locals 600-999, 1949 November; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 90-130)
    - Over-the-Road: Central States Drivers Council-Strikes, Clippings, 1949 November; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 131)
    - Over-the-Road: Eastern States Transportation Council, 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 132)
    - Over-the-Road: Southwest Over-the-Road and General Teamsters Council, 1942-1943 June; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 133)
    - Over-the-Road: Southwest Over-the-Road and General Teamsters Council, 1943 July-1944; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 134)
    - Over-the-Road: Highway Drivers Council of California, 1941; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 63, Segment 135)
    - Over-the-Road: Highway Drivers Council of California, 1942-1945; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 1)
    - Over-the-Road: Indiana State Drivers Council, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 2)
    - Over-the-Road: Missouri-Kansas Highway Drivers Counci1, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 3)
    - Over-the-Road: Ohio Highway Drivers Council, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 4)
    - Over-the-Road: Ohio Highway Drivers Council - Dispute with CSDC, 1947-1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 5)
    - Over-the-Road: Ohio Highway Drivers Council - Dispute with CSDC, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 6)
    - Over-the-Road: Ohio Highway Drivers Council - Dispute with CSDC, 1951-1952, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 7)
    - Over-the-Road: Wisconsin State Drivers Conference, 1942, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 8)
    - Petroleum: Indiana Statewide Petroleum Transport Agreement, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 9)
    - Petroleum: Midwest Petroleum Union Conference, 1941-1947; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 10)
    - Petroleum: Northwest Petroleum Conference, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 11)
    - Petroleum: Petroleum Drivers Conference See also Automotive, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 12)
    - Truckaway: National Truckaway and Driveaway Conference, 1943 July-1944; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 13)
    - Warehouse: National Warehouse Conference, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Reel 64, Segment 14)
- American Federation of Labor correspondence, 1905-1952; Series 3; 11 microfilm reels
  This series, one of the more complete in the collection, consisting primarily of correspondence with some minutes, reports, and related papers. The most important and frequently discussed subjects are jurisdictional problems and disputes, organizing campaigns, relations with the CIO, national affairs and politics, conditions of labor, and the state of the labor movement. The correspondents for the I.B.T. are usually Tobin, Hughes, Gillespie, or Flynn. Tobin's correspondence in his capacity as AFL treasurer is contained in the Staff Correspondence, Daniel J. Tobin files.